



Godswill Oghenero Udezi

O Home: Campus Hub, Msida, Level 4-5, West Block, 6 M. Mangion, San Giljan, STJ 3180, Valletta, Malta

Email: <u>neroudezi@gmail.com</u> **◇ Phone:** (+356) 99431440

Date of birth: 27 Jul 1992 Nationality: Nigerian (Nigeria)

ABOUT ME

Highly skilled Professional with a lustrum worth of experience in Business development and Management. I am equipped with the necessary skills and deep understanding of the software development lifecycle, from design and implementation to testing and deployment.

WORK EXPERIENCE

[17 Nov 2016 – 10 Feb 2017] **Data Aggregator**

Adamawa State Government www.adamawastate.gov.ng

City: Yola, Adamawa State | Country: Nigeria | Name of unit or department: Ministry of Budget and Economic Planning | **Business or sector:** Public administration and defence; compulsory social security

Responsibilities includes systematically gathering, verifying, and organizing data through various methods, ensuring its accuracy and completeness. I perform data quality assurance, create detailed reports, and uphold data privacy and security standards while collaborating with teams to fulfill their data requirements.

[1 Nov 2018 – 28 Jul 2021]

Managing director

Excelyn Water Company

City: Lagos | Country: Nigeria | Name of unit or department: Managerial Role **Business or sector:** Manufacturing

Delivered strategic leadership, oversee financial management, lead the executive team, ensure operational efficiency, drive business growth, engage with key stakeholders, ensure compliance and risk management, and uphold ethical standards to guide the organization to success.

[18 Oct 2021 – 6 Nov 2023]

Software developer

Freelancer www.oghenero.dev

City: Lagos | Country: Nigeria | Email address: Hello@Oghenero.dev | Name of unit or department: FullStack

Designing and developing web applications from front-end to server-side, creating user-friendly and visually appealing interfaces, managing databases, developing APIs, ensuring code quality, security, and performance, collaborating with crossfunctional teams, and documenting the entire system architecture.

[8]an 2024 – 30 Mar 2024] **Front-end Developer**

Entelligence https://entelligence.uk/

City: Lagos | Country: Nigeria

Collaborated with the development team to design and build client-side prototypes. Engaged with clients throughout the development process to ensure their requirements were met. Translated client feedback into functional and user-friendly prototypes, and rigorously tested them to meet client specifications and quality

standards. Worked closely with UI/UX designers who designed the final product based on the built prototype.

EDUCATION AND TRAIN-ING

[12 Sep 2012 – 7 Aug 2016] **Bsc Economics**

KWAME NKRUMAH UNIVERSITY https://www.knust.edu.gh/

City: Kumasi | Country: Ghana |

[4 Feb 2017 – 10 Nov 2017] **Graduate Certificate in Management**

NIGERIAN INSTITUTE OF MANAGEMENT https://nim.ng

City: Lagos, | Country: Nigeria |

[25 May 2024 – Current] MBA Project Management

GBS MALTA https://gbs.edu.mt/
City: Valletta | Country: Malta |

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): English

Other language(s):

Yoruba, Isoko

LISTENING C2 READING C2 WRITING C2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION C2 SPOKEN INTERACTION C2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

DIGITAL SKILLS

My Digital Skills

Backend development | Database integration | Trello | Information management | Digital communication tools | Front-end Techologies | Programming